{
  "author": "thelupineone",
  "rounds": [
    {
      "roundTitle": "Oh ye Gods! My roast is ruined!",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Played C.J. Parker on Baywatch",
          "correctAnswer": "Pamela Anderson"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Portrayed Captain James T. Kirk on the original series of Star Trek",
          "correctAnswer": "William Shatner"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "American rapper, founding member of Public Enemy, often wears a clock around his neck in place of a medallion",
          "correctAnswer": "Flavor Flav"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Portrayed Danny Tanner on Full House",
          "correctAnswer": "Bob Saget"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "American comedian who won the Daytime Emmy for Outstanding Talk Show Host in 1990",
          "correctAnswer": "Joan Rivers"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Played Michael Knight, the man behind the wheel of KITT on Knight Rider",
          "correctAnswer": "David Hasselhoff"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Starred in 'Two and a Half Men' between 2003 and 2011 before his dismissal from the series, resulting in a public meltdown",
          "correctAnswer": "Charlie Sheen"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The voice of Mater in Pixar's 'Cars' series of animated movies",
          "correctAnswer": "Larry the Cable Guy"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Played Harry Osborn in the Sam Raimi-directed Spider-Man movie trilogy",
          "correctAnswer": "James Franco"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Canadian pop singer whose hits include 'Baby', 'Love Yourself' and 'What Do You Mean?'",
          "correctAnswer": "Justin Bieber"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Played John McClane in the Die Hard movie franchise",
          "correctAnswer": "Bruce Willis"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Played Jack Donaghy in the Tina Fey sitcom 30 Rock",
          "correctAnswer": "Alec Baldwin"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Denis Leary",
        "Donald Trump",
        "Roseanne Barr",
        "Rob Lowe"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "But what if... I were to purchase fast food and disguise it as my own cooking?",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Chicken Fries",
          "correctAnswer": "Burger King"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Tiny Tacos",
          "correctAnswer": "Jack in the Box"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Dave's Single",
          "correctAnswer": "Wendy's"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Big Buford",
          "correctAnswer": "Checkers / Rally's"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Concrete Mixer",
          "correctAnswer": "Culver's"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Double-Double",
          "correctAnswer": "In-N-Out Burger"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Mexican Pizza",
          "correctAnswer": "Taco Bell"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Chicken Little",
          "correctAnswer": "KFC"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Crazy Bread",
          "correctAnswer": "Little Caesars"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Blizzard",
          "correctAnswer": "Dairy Queen"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Classic Beef 'N Cheddar",
          "correctAnswer": "Arby's"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The 3 Finger Combo",
          "correctAnswer": "Raising Cane's"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "McDonald's",
        "Carl's Jr. / Hardee's",
        "Panera Bread",
        "Tim Hortons"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Good Lord, what is happening in there?",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "A creature from Irish folklore, said to reveal the location of treasure if caught",
          "correctAnswer": "Leprechaun"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A dwelling infested with ghosts",
          "correctAnswer": "Haunted House"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "An Australian cryptid also known as the Yarri",
          "correctAnswer": "Queensland Tiger"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Encountered by the Fellowship of the Ring in the Mines of Moria",
          "correctAnswer": "The Balrog"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A 1983 novel by Roald Dahl",
          "correctAnswer": "The Witches"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "It's why the pitch of an ambulance's siren changes as it approaches and then moves away from you",
          "correctAnswer": "The Doppler Effect"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Enemies respawn under its red glow in The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild",
          "correctAnswer": "Blood Moon"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A 1982 horror movie co-written by Steven Spielberg",
          "correctAnswer": "Poltergeist"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Humans that transform into lupine form under the light of a full moon",
          "correctAnswer": "Werewolves"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Will o' the Wisp",
        "Mothman",
        "The Babadook"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Well, Seymour, you are an odd fellow, but I must say... you steam a good ham.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six breeds of pig named on the article 'Top 15 Best Pig Breeds for Your Farm' on agronomag.com",
          "correctAnswer": "Mulefoot"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six breeds of pig named on the article 'Top 15 Best Pig Breeds for Your Farm' on agronomag.com",
          "correctAnswer": "Duroc"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six breeds of pig named on the article 'Top 15 Best Pig Breeds for Your Farm' on agronomag.com",
          "correctAnswer": "American Yorkshire"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six breeds of pig named on the article 'Top 15 Best Pig Breeds for Your Farm' on agronomag.com",
          "correctAnswer": "Gloucestershire Old Spots"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six breeds of pig named on the article 'Top 15 Best Pig Breeds for Your Farm' on agronomag.com",
          "correctAnswer": "Chester White"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six breeds of pig named on the article 'Top 15 Best Pig Breeds for Your Farm' on agronomag.com",
          "correctAnswer": "Tamworth"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Simmental",
        "Belted Galloway",
        "Limousin",
        "Khaki Campbell",
        "Jersey Giant",
        "Orpington",
        "Wyandotte",
        "Sussex",
        "Lincoln",
        "Merino"
      ]
    }
  ]
}